Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alumni files, 1889-2005; RG0026 Series 21; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  - Alumni - Young Alumni Council, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - History of GW - Foggy Bottom Neighborhood - Hamburg - Booklet "Hamburg" by Jesse Fant Evans 1935 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Students - senior class activities, 1922 ca.-1974 ca. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0026 Series 22; 7.5 Linear feet
  This series contains photographs, biographical sketches, articles and newsletters. The subjects of these photographs include Founder's Day celebrations, Alumni Reunions, Dean Robert Kramer, Dean Jack Friedenthal, Harold Green, Patricia Roberts Harris, Joyce Green, Earl Warren, Oliver Gasch, Warren Burger, Leon Jaworski, John Duncan, Sarah Hughes, Oswald Colclough, Lloyd Elliott, Van Vleck moot court, receptions, Jacob Burns, and buildings.
- GW Impact, report on Philanthropy, Summer-Spring 2010; RG0026 Series 23; 0.25 Linear Feet
  GW Impact is published by the Division of Development and Alumni Relations. The publication celebrates the alumni, parents, friends, and organizations who have made a philanthropic investment in The George Washington University and its future. Issues date from 2009 to 2010.
  - GW Impact, Summer 2009, RG0026 Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GW Impact, Fall 2009, RG0026 Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GW Impact, Winter 2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GW Impact, Spring 2010; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GW Impact, Summer 2011-Winter 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- File on alumni who died on 9/11/2001, RG 0026 series 24; 1 folder(s) (Box 1)
  Contains letters of condolence, a message from President Trachtenberg, obituaries and other research on alumni who died in the September 11 attacks.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Received from the office of alumni relations in 2016. Accession no. 2016.089.
- Newsletters, Series 25; 0.25 Linear Feet (Box 1)
  - Alumni Newsletter, 1989-1992; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Events, 1991-2003; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mount Vernon Today, 2007-2012; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)